[{"answer": " Jared?  Hi, Im Doctor Brown", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Nice to meet you doctor", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 12, "question": " Jared?  Hi, Im Doctor Brown", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Now, what seems to be the problem today", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Nice to meet you doctor", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Well, I have this rash on my arms and chest", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Now, what seems to be the problem today", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " I see.  How long have you had it", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Well, I have this rash on my arms and chest", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Two weeks", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 16, "question": " I see.  How long have you had it", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Were you doing anything unusual before you got the rash?  Anything you ca", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Two weeks", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " I dont think so.  I cant think of anything", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Were you doing anything unusual before you got the rash?  Anything you ca", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Does it itch", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 22, "question": " I dont think so.  I cant think of anything", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Yes, it itches a lot", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Does it itch", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " And are you having any other symptoms", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Yes, it itches a lot", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Well, Ive been having headaches for the past week", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 28, "question": " And are you having any other symptoms", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " How would you describe the pain of your headache", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 29, "question": " Well, Ive been having headaches for the past week", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " I guess a throbbing pain", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 30, "question": " How would you describe the pain of your headache", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " All right.  It sounds like you might have an infection that is causing the ras", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 31, "question": " I guess a throbbing pain", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": "Ive been using an anti-itch ointment for the rash", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 35, "question": " All right.  It sounds like you might have an infection that is causing the ras", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " Has that been helping", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Ive been using an anti-itch ointment for the rash", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Not really", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Has that been helping", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " OK.  We can give you a prescription for something stronger that should help", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Not really", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 42, "question": " OK.  We can give you a prescription for something stronger that should help", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Do you smoke", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 43, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " No", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Do you smoke", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Do you drink alcohol", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 45, "question": " No", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Occasionally.  Maybe a few drinks on the weekends", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Do you drink alcohol", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " OK.  Any illnesses in your immediate family", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Occasionally.  Maybe a few drinks on the weekends", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Well, my dad has diabetes and my mom passed away from lung cancer", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 48, "question": " OK.  Any illnesses in your immediate family", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Im sorry to hear that.  How old was she when she was diagnosed", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Well, my dad has diabetes and my mom passed away from lung cancer", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " I think she was 45.  She died when she was 50", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Im sorry to hear that.  How old was she when she was diagnosed", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " All right.  Have you had any serious illnesses or surgery", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I think she was 45.  She died when she was 50", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " No.  Oh, wait.  I did break my arm when I was 15.  I had to have surgery for that", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 52, "question": " All right.  Have you had any serious illnesses or surgery", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Were there any problems or complications", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 53, "question": " No.  Oh, wait.  I did break my arm when I was 15.  I had to have surgery for that", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": "No", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Were there any problems or complications", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " OK.  And are you allergic to any medications", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 58, "question": "No", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Not that I know of", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 59, "question": " OK.  And are you allergic to any medications", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Very good.  Im going to prescribe you an antibiotic that should clear up an", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Not that I know of", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " What if I forget to take a dose", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Very good.  Im going to prescribe you an antibiotic that should clear up an", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Just resume taking the medicine at the next scheduled time.  You should als", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 65, "question": " What if I forget to take a dose", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Just resume taking the medicine at the next scheduled time.  You should als", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Do you have any questions or anything else I can help you with today", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 69, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " No, I think thats it", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Do you have any questions or anything else I can help you with today", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " All right.  Take care now and make sure to come back if the rash doesnt clea", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 71, "question": " No, I think thats it", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " OK, I will.  Thank you", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 75, "question": " All right.  Take care now and make sure to come back if the rash doesnt clea", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Bye-bye", "docId": "10-09", "aSentId": 76, "question": " OK, I will.  Thank you", "qSentId": 75}]
